A Guide to the Correspondence of the Speaker of the House of Delegates, 1960-1980.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence of the Speaker of the House of Delegates, 1960-1980 (Accession 30670)., Extent: 13.3 cubic feet (38 boxes)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1976-1978. (Box 38)
  - Visually Handicapped, Virginia Commisison for the, 1977. (Box 38)
  - Water Control Board, 1973-1974. (Box 38)
  - Welfare Reform Act, 1977. (Box 38)
  - Women, House of Delegates, 1979. (Box 38)
  - World War II Memorial Commission, 1968. (Box 38)
  - York River Basin Advisory Committee, 1975. (Box 38)
  - Plans - Facilities for the General Assembly of Virginia [Remodeling Life of Virginia Buidling], 1969-1976.
    - Design Development Phase - Architectural, plumbling, mechanical and electrical. Scale 1/8 inch to 1 foot. 64 sheets, Blueline, 30 x 42, 1976 Jan. (Box 1)
    - Plumbing, HVAC, demolition, and lighting plans. Scale 1/8 inch to 1 foot. 63 sheets, (missing sheet E-26), Blueline, 30 x 42, 1976 June. (Box 2)
    - Plumbing, HVAC, demolition, and lighting plans. Scale 1/8 inch to 1 foot. 62 sheets, (missing sheets E-28 and E-29), Blueline, 30 x 42, 1976 June. (Box 3)
    - Ninth Floor Plan, Revised. Scale 1/8 inch to 1 foot. 5 sheets, Blueline, 30 x 42, 1976 June. (Box 4)
    - Facilities for the Appropriations Committee. Scale 1/8 inch to 1 foot. 2 sheets, Blueline, 20 x 24, 1976 Aug. (Box 5)
    - New Offices for Attorney General. Scale 1/4 inch to 1 foot. 3 sheets, Blueline, 30 x 42, 1976 Au. (Box 6)
    - Fourth Floor Plan - New Construction - Member Offices. Scale 1/8 inch to 1 foot. 1 sheet, Blueline, 30 x 42, 1976 June. (Box 7)
    - Renovations to Richmond West Hotel, Floors 6-10. No scale given. 5 sheets, Blueline, 23 x 21, 1969. (Box 8)